Hi, I'm Jennifer Cail.
Now that our butter has been creamed it's time to add the next ingredients.
We are going to add 3/4 of a cup of sugar, you happen to have an odd size 3/4 cup measuring cup that is always much easier to work with.
Otherwise you'll use your half cup and your 1/4 cup to measure and you just want to scoop the sugar into your cup.
It's granulated sugar so you don't have to worry about packing it down or not.
Then pour it into your butter mixture or the creamed butter.
We are going to start your mixer on a lower speed to just start incorporating a little bit this is going to cause it to be almost like clumps of butter surrounded by the sugar.
Then you are going to turn the mixer up just a little bit.
Now with our butter and sugar fully incorporated you can see that it's a nice fluffy consistency.
You'll probably need to scrape the bowl down at least once will beating it to make sure to get all of the butter off.
Now it's ready for the next step.